PENNY:
Okay.
(Penny:)Nope. That's it.
(Penny:)We are gonna go
over there right now.
(Penny:)And you are going
to let them out.
(Dr Lorvis:)Three Mississippi,
four Mississippi...
Move it!
(Bernadette:)Oh, good, you're here.
(Bernadette:)Amy, I am so sorry.
(Amy:)That has to wait.
This weirdo locked
(Amy:)the guys up in his basement.
What?!
(Dr Lorvis:)She seems nice. Who's she?
Just walk.
SHELDON:
You can do this.
One ladder left!
Oh-ho! Yeah!
Yes!
Next level!
(Penny:)Leonard, are you okay?
Better than okay.
I am having the game of my life!
(Amy:)Dr. Lorvis, isn't there
something you want to say?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Dr Lorvis:)I'm very sorry
for locking you in my home.
(Howard:)Yeah, that was very uncool.
Get the hammer!
(Leonard:)Got it.
(guys cheering)
Okay, Leonard, let's go!
J-Just hang on!
(Dr Lorvis:)Well, while we wait,
(Dr Lorvis:)would you like to see Tobey
Maguire's prostate sonogram?
(Bernadette:)Sure.
Yeah.
(Dr Lorvis:)Oh, spoiler alert.
Uh, he was worried
about nothing.